{
  "Name": "Letters",
  "Cards": [
    {
      "QuestionText": "A",
      "AnswerText": "A"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "B",
      "AnswerText": "B"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "C",
      "AnswerText": "C"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "D",
      "AnswerText": "D"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "E",
      "AnswerText": "E"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "F",
      "AnswerText": "F"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "G",
      "AnswerText": "G"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "H",
      "AnswerText": "H"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "I",
      "AnswerText": "I"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "J",
      "AnswerText": "J"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "K",
      "AnswerText": "K"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "L",
      "AnswerText": "L"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "M",
      "AnswerText": "M"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "N",
      "AnswerText": "N"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "O",
      "AnswerText": "O"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "P",
      "AnswerText": "P"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "Q",
      "AnswerText": "Q"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "R",
      "AnswerText": "R"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "S",
      "AnswerText": "S"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "T",
      "AnswerText": "T"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "U",
      "AnswerText": "U"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "V",
      "AnswerText": "V"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "W",
      "AnswerText": "W"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "X",
      "AnswerText": "X"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "Y",
      "AnswerText": "Y"
    },
    {
      "QuestionText": "Z",
      "AnswerText": "Z"
    }
  ]
}
